Finding Aid for President (University of Michigan) records, 1967-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files 1967/68-2008/09
  - 1968-1969
    - Washtenaw County (Box 11)
    - Wayne County Community College (Box 11)
    - Wayne State University (Box 11)
    - Williams, Robert L. (Administrative Dean, Academic Affairs) (Box 11)
    - Willow Run Airport Laboratories (Box 11)
    - Wills (Box 11)
    - XYZ-General (Box 11)
  - 1969-1970
    - A (General) (Box 12)
    - Accreditation (Box 12)
    - Acts/Bills (Glossary) (Box 12)
    - Admissions Office (Box 12)
    - Affirmative Action Programs (Box 12)
    - Africa, Junior Year Abroad (Box 12)
    - Afro-American Studies Program (Box 12)
    - Alumni Association (Box 12)
    - American (Box 12)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) (Box 12)
    - American Association of University Women (AAUW) (Box 12)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) (Box 12)
    - American Council on Education (ACE) (Box 12)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 12)
    - Anonymous/Asylum (letters) (Box 12)
    - Architecture and Design, College of (Box 12)
    - Association of American Colleges (Box 12)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 12)
    - Athletics (Box 12)
    - Attorney's Office (Box 12)
    - Awards (glossary) (Box 12)
    - B-General (Box 12)
    - Band (University) (Box 12)
    - Bentley (A.M. & H.P.) Chair in History (Box 12)
    - Black (faculty/students) (Box 12)
    - Blues Festival (Box 12)
    - Brown, Robert J. (Regent) (Box 12)
    - Buildings (classrooms and offices) (Box 12)
    - Bureaus (Box 12)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 12)
    - Bylaws (Box 12)
    - C-General (Box 12)
    - Cash, William L., Jr. (Assistant to the President for Human Relations Affairs) (Box 12)
    - Centers (Glossary) (Box 12)
    - Collections (Box 12)
    - Commendations and Congratulations (Box 12)
    - Committees
      - External (Glossary) (Box 12)
      - Internal (Glossary) (Box 12)
      - Council for Financial Aid to Education (Box 12)
    - Complaints
      - Disruptions (Box 12)
      - President Fleming (about) (Box 12)
      - General, 3 folders (Box 12)
    - Condolence Letters (Box 12)
    - Conflict of Interest (Box 12)
    - Consortia (Box 12)
    - Cooperative, University (Box 12)
    - Corporate Responsibility (Box 12)
    - Council of Ten (Committee on Institutional Cooperation) (Box 12)
    - Course Evaluation (Box 12)
    - Cudlip, William B. (Regent) (Box 12)
    - D-General (Box 13)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 13)
    - Detroit (Box 13)
    - Development Office/Development Council (Box 13)
    - Discipline (Student/Faculty) (Box 13)
    - Disruptions
      - Complaints (Box 13)
      - Other Schools (Box 13)
      - General (Box 13)
    - Drugs (Box 13)
    - E-General (Box 13)
    - Economic Opportunity (Information & Programs) (Box 13)
    - Education, School of (Box 13)
    - Endowments (Box 13)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 13)
    - Environment (Teach-In-Enact) (Box 13)
    - Estates (Box 13)
    - Exchange Programs (Box 13)
    - Extension Service (Box 13)
    - F-General (Box 13)
    - Fees (Box 13)
    - Fellowships/Scholarships
      - External (Box 13)
      - Internal (Box 13)
    - Financial Aid, Office of (Box 13)
    - Fleming, Robben W. (President)
      - Accolades (Box 13)
      - Statements and Miscellaneous Notes (Box 13)
      - Personal (Box 13)
    - Flint College (plus Citizens Committee and Community Colleges) (Box 13)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 13)
    - Fricke, Benno (Director, Evaluations and Examinations Office) (Box 13)
    - Fundraising Programs (Box 13)
    - Funds/Gifts (Glossary) (Box 13)
    - G-General (Box 13)
    - Gay Liberation Front (Box 13)
    - Goebel, Paul G. (Regent) (Box 13)
    - Governing Boards, Association of (Box 13)
    - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of (Box 13)
    - H-General (Box 13)
    - Haber, William (Advisor to Executive Officers) (Box 13)
    - Housing (Faculty/Student) (Box 13)
    - Hubbard, William N. (Dean, Medical School) (Box 13)
    - Huebner, Gertrude V. (Regent) (Box 13)
    - I-General (Box 13)
    - Institutes
      - External (Box 13)
      - Internal--Highway Safety Research Institute (Box 13)
    - Inter-University Committee on Travel Grants (Box 13)
    - Introduction, Letters of (Box 13)
    - J-General (Box 13)
    - K-General (Box 13)
    - Kellogg (W.K.) Foundation (Box 13)
    - King, Martin Luther, Fund (Box 13)
    - L-General (Box 14)
    - Law School (Box 14)
    - Library, University (including School of Library Science) (Box 14)
    - Lindemer, Lawrence B. (Regent) (Box 14)
    - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of (Box 14)
    - M-General (Box 14)
    - Medical Center (Box 14)
    - Medical School (Box 14)
    - Metropolitan Fund (Box 14)
    - Michigan, State of (Box 14)
    - Michigan Coordinating Board for Higher Education (Box 14)
    - Michigan Council of State College Presidents (Box 14)
    - Michigan Daily Newsclippings (Box 14)
    - Michigan Legislature, Committee Members (Box 14)
    - Michigan Rendezvous, Expo '70 (Box 14)
    - Michigan Society of Fellows (Box 14)
    - Michigan State Offices
      - Executive Offices, Departments, Divisions (Box 14)
      - Department of Education (Box 14)
    - Michigan-State Plan for Higher Education (Box 14)
    - Michigan State University (Box 14)
    - Michigan Union (Box 14)
    - Midwestern Universities Research Association (MURA) (Box 14)
    - Milliken, William G. (Michigan Governor) (Box 14)
    - Minorities (Box 14)
    - Mott, C.S. Harding (Box 14)
    - Mott (C.S.) Children's Hospital (Box 14)
    - Murders (in Ann Arbor area) (Box 14)
    - Museums, University (Box 14)
    - Music, School of (Box 14)
    - N-General (Box 14)
    - National (Box 14)
    - National Association of State Universities & Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 14)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF) (Box 14)
    - Natural Resources, School of (Box 14)
    - Nederlander, Robert E. (Regent) (Box 14)
    - Negro (Box 14)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (U.S. President) (Box 14)
    - Norman, A.G. (Vice President for Research) (Box 14)
    - O-General (Box 15)
    - Opportunity Award Program (Box 15)
    - Osteopathic Medicine (Box 15)
    - P-General (Box 15)
    - Pierpont, Wilbur K. (Vice President and Chief Financial Officer) (Box 15)
    - Political Process, Student Participation in (Box 15)
    - President's Club (Box 15)
    - President's Letters, Reports, etc. (Box 15)
    - "Princeton Plan" (Box 15)
    - Programs (new or proposed) (Box 15)
    - Q-General (Box 15)
    - Quaal, Ward L. (Box 15)
    - Questionnaires (Box 15)
    - R-General (Box 15)
    - Radock, Michael (Vice President for University Relations) (Box 15)
    - Recruitment (Box 15)
    - Regents, Board of (Box 15)
    - Requests (Unusual) (Box 15)
    - Research, Office of Vice President for (A.G. Norman) (Box 15)
    - Research (Classified/Unclassified) (Box 15)
    - Rose Bowl (Box 15)
    - ROTC (Reserve Officers Training Corps) (Box 15)
    - S-General (Box 15)
    - Senate, Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 15)
    - Saginaw Valley College (Box 15)
    - St. Joseph Mercy Hospital (Box 15)
    - S.D.S. (Students for Democratic Society) (Box 15)
    - Selective Service (Box 15)
    - Senate, Senate Assembly, SACUA (Box 15)
    - Smith, Otis M. (Regent) (Box 15)
    - Spurr, Stephen H. (Dean, Rackham) (Box 15)
    - Students (Aid, Activities, Rights, Role) (Box 15)
    - Student Affairs, Office of Vice President for (Acting Vice President B. Newell) (Box 15)
    - Student Government Council (SGC) (Box 15)
    - Student Organizations (Box 15)
    - Student Publications (Box 15)
    - Students for Effective Action (SEA) (Box 15)
    - Study Abroad Program (Box 15)
    - Surveys (Box 15)
    - T-General (Box 15)
    - Tarrant, Shawn (Housing) (Box 15)
    - Teaching Fellows (Box 15)
    - Theatre (Box 15)
    - Tonsor, Stephen (Professor) (Box 15)
    - Tutorial Project (Box 15)
    - U-General (Box 15)
    - Unions (Box 15)
    - United States
      - Congress (members) (Box 15)
      - Governmental Departments & Agencies (Box 15)
      - Department of Health, Education & Welfare (HEW) (Box 15)
    - Universities Research Association, Inc. (Box 15)
    - University of Michigan (Accolades and Criticism) (Box 15)
    - University Center for Adult Education (UCAE) (Box 15)
    - University Hospital (Box 15)
    - V-General (Box 16)
    - Vietnam (Box 16)
    - W-General (Box 16)
    - Walter, Erich A. (Assistant Emeritus to the President) (Box 16)
    - Washtenaw County (Box 16)
    - Wayne County Community College (Box 16)
    - Wayne State University (Box 16)
    - Wheeler, Albert H. (Professor) (Box 16)
    - Williams, Robert L. (Administrative Dean, Academic Affairs) (Box 16)
    - Willow Run Laboratories (Box 16)
    - XYZ-General (Box 16)
  - 1970-1971
    - A-General (Box 16)
    - Academic Affairs Advisory Council (Box 16)
    - Academic Affairs, Office of Vice President for (Allan F. Smith) (Box 16)
    - Accreditation (Box 16)
    - Acts/Bills (Glossary) (Box 16)
    - Admissions (Box 16)
    - Affirmative Action Programs (Box 16)
    - Africa (Box 16)
    - Afro-American Studies Program (Box 16)
    - Alumni Association (Box 16)
    - American (Box 16)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) (Box 16)
    - American Council on Education (ACE) (Box 16)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 16)
    - Anonymous/Asylum (letters) (Box 16)
    - Appointments/Promotions Procedures (Box 16)
    - Architecture and Design, College of (Box 16)
    - Argonne Universities Association (Box 16)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 17)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Council on Federal Relations (Box 17)
    - Association of Governing Boards (Box 17)
    - Athletics
      - General (Box 17)
      - Women (Box 17)
    - Attorney's Office (Box 17)
    - Autonomy (Box 17)
    - Awards (Box 17)
    - B-General (Box 17)
    - Band (University) (Box 17)
    - Black (faculty/students) (Box 17)
    - Blues Festival (Box 17)
    - Brown, Robert J. (Regent) (Box 17)
    - Budget (Statistics) (Box 17)
    - Budgeting (Box 17)
    - Buildings (classrooms and offices) (Box 17)
    - Bureaus (Box 17)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 17)
    - Bylaws (Box 17)
    - C-General (Box 17)
    - Carnegie Commission on Higher Education (Box 18)
    - Cash, William L., Jr. (Assistant to the President for Human Relations Affairs) (Box 18)
    - Centers (Glossary) (Box 18)
    - Christensen, Craig W. (University Attorney) (Box 18)
    - Clements Library (Box 18)
    - Cohen, Wilbur J. (Dean, School of Education) (Box 18)
    - Collections (Box 18)
    - Commendations and Congratulations (Box 18)
    - Committees
      - External (Glossary) (Box 18)
      - Internal (Glossary) (Box 18)
    - Community Colleges (Box 18)
    - Complaints
      - Disruptions (Box 18)
      - President Fleming (about) (Box 18)
      - General, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Computer Network (Box 18)
    - Condolence Letters (Box 18)
    - Conflict of Interest (Box 18)
    - Consortia (Box 18)
    - Cordish, Joel (Box 18)
    - Corporate Responsibility (Box 18)
    - Council for Financial Aid to Education (Box 18)
    - Council of Ten (Committee on Institutional Cooperation) (Box 18)
    - Cudlip, William B. (Regent) (Box 18)
    - Cutler, Richard L. (Special Assistant for Urban Affairs) (Box 18)
    - D-General (Box 19)
    - Deans, Letters to (Box 19)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 19)
    - Detroit (Box 19)
    - Development Office/Development Council (Box 19)
    - Discipline (Students/Faculty) (Box 19)
    - Discrimination (Box 19)
    - Disruptions
      - Complaints (Box 19)
      - Other Schools (Box 19)
      - General (Box 19)
    - Drugs (Box 19)
    - Dunn, Gerald R. (Regent) (Box 19)
    - E-General (Box 19)
    - Education, School of (Box 19)
    - EDUCOM (Box 19)
    - Engineering College (Box 19)
    - Environment (includes ENACT) (Box 19)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity (Box 19)
    - Estates (Box 19)
    - Exchange Programs (Box 19)
    - Executive Officers (Box 19)
    - Expeditions (Box 19)
    - Extension Service (Box 19)
    - F-General (Box 19)
    - Faculty Reform Coalition (Box 19)
    - Fauri, Fedele F. (Vice President for State Relations and Planning) (Box 19)
    - Fees (Box 19)
    - Fellowships/Scholarships
      - External (Box 19)
      - Internal (Box 19)
    - Financial Aid, Office of (Box 19)
    - Fleming, Robben W. (President)
      - Accolades (Box 19)
      - Statements and Miscellaneous Notes (Box 19)
      - Personal (Box 19)
    - Flint College (includes Citizens Committee and Community Colleges) (Box 19)
    - Football (Social Activities) (Box 19)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 19)
    - Foreign Student Inquiries (Box 19)
    - Francis, Thomas, Jr., M.D. (Box 19)
    - G-General (Box 20)
    - Gay Liberation Front (Box 20)
    - Goebel, Paul G. (Regent) (Box 20)
    - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of (Box 20)
    - Grievances (Box 20)
    - Gun Collection (Box 20)
    - H-General (Box 20)
    - Haber, William (Advisor to Executive Officers) (Box 20)
    - Health Service, University (Box 20)
    - Historical Collections (Michigan Historical Collections) (Box 20)
    - Honors Convocations (Box 20)
    - Housing (Faculty & Student) (Box 20)
    - I-General (Box 20)
    - Institutes
      - External (Box 20)
      - Internal
        - General (Box 20)
        - Institute for Social Research (ISR) (Box 20)
    - Institutional Research, Office of (Box 20)
    - Introduction, Letters of (Box 20)
    - J-General (Box 20)
    - Judiciary (University) (Box 20)
    - K-General (Box 20)
    - Kennedy, Richard L. (Secretary of the University, Assistant to the President) (Box 20)
    - King (Martin Luther) Fund (Box 20)
    - L-General (Box 20)
    - Law School (Box 20)
    - Library, University (includes School of Library Science) (Box 20)
    - Lindemer, Lawrence B. (Regent) (Box 20)
    - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of
      - General (Box 20)
      - Departments (Box 20)
    - M-General (Box 20)
    - Maddox, Gilbert A. (Box 20)
    - Medical Center (Box 21)
    - Medical School (Box 21)
    - Metropolitan Fund (Box 21)
    - Michigan, State of (Box 21)
    - Michigan Council of State College Presidents (Box 21)
    - Michigan Daily (Box 21)
    - Michigan Legislature, Committee Members (Box 21)
    - Michigan Society of Fellows (Box 21)
    - Michigan State Offices
      - Executive Offices, Departments, Divisions (Box 21)
      - Department of Education (Box 21)
    - Michigan State University (Box 21)
    - Midwestern Universities Research Association (MURA) (Box 21)
    - Minorities (Box 21)
    - Mott (C.S.) Foundation (Box 21)
    - Music, School of (Box 21)
    - N-General (Box 21)
    - National (Box 21)
    - National Association of State Universities & Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 21)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF) (Box 21)
    - Nederlander, Robert E. (Regent) (Box 22)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (U.S. President) (Box 22)
    - O-General (Box 22)
    - Opportunity Award Program (Box 22)
    - Optometry, School of (proposed) (Box 22)
    - Orientation (Box 22)
    - Outstanding Achievement Awards (Box 22)
    - P-General (Box 22)
    - Personnel Office (Box 22)
    - Pierpont, Wilbur K. (Vice President and Chief Financial Officer) (Box 22)
    - Planning, Long-Range (Box 22)
    - Plant Extension (Box 22)
    - Political Activity (Student Participation) (Box 22)
    - Power, Eugene B. (Box 22)
    - President's Club (Box 22)
    - President's Letters, Reports, etc. (Box 22)
    - Professorships (Glossary) (Box 22)
    - Programs (new or proposed) (Box 22)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 22)
    - Q-General (Box 22)
    - Questionnaires (Box 22)
    - R-General (Box 22)
    - Radock, Michael (Vice President for University Relations) (Box 22)
    - Recruiting (Box 22)
    - Regents, Board of (Box 22)
    - Requests (Unusual) (Box 22)
    - Research, Office of Vice President for (A.G. Norman) (Box 22)
    - Research Administration, Office of (Box 22)
    - Research (Classified/Unclassified) (Box 22)
    - Residential College (Box 22)
    - Ross, Arthur M. (Box 23)
    - ROTC (Reserve Officers Training Corps) (Box 23)
    - Ruthven, Alexander G. (President Emeritus) (Box 23)
    - S-General (Box 23)
    - S.D.S. (Students for Democratic Society) (Box 23)
    - Sea Grant Program (Box 23)
    - Security (Box 23)
    - SEMCOG (Southeast Michigan Council of Governments) (Box 23)
    - Senate (University), Senate Assembly, SACUA
      - General (Box 23)
      - Minutes (Box 23)
    - Smith, Otis M. (Regent) (Box 23)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 23)
    - Solstis School (Box 23)
    - Spurr, Stephen H. (Vice President and Dean of Graduate Studies) (Box 23)
    - Student Government Council (Box 23)
    - Student Organizations (Box 23)
    - Student Publications (including Michigan Daily) (Box 23)
    - Student Services, Office of Vice President for (Robert L. Knauss) (Box 23)
    - T-General (Box 23)
    - Tax-Exempt Status of Universities (Box 23)
    - Teaching Fellows (Box 23)
    - Theatre (Box 23)
    - Trimester (Box 23)
    - Tropical Studies, Organization for (OTS) (Box 23)
    - U-General (Box 24)
    - Unions (Box 24)
    - United States
      - Congress (members of) (Box 24)
      - Governmental Departments and Agencies (Box 24)
      - Department of Health, Education & Welfare (HEW) (Box 24)
    - Universities Research Association, Inc. (Box 24)
    - University (Accolades and Criticism) (Box 24)
    - University Musical Society (UMS) (Box 24)
    - University Press (Box 24)
    - V-General (Box 24)
    - Van Wylen, Gordon J. (Dean, College of Engineering) (Box 24)
    - Vietnam (Box 24)
    - Visitors (Box 24)
    - W-General (Box 24)
    - Washtenaw County (Box 24)
    - Waters, James L. (Regent) (Box 24)
    - Wayne State University (Box 24)
    - WCBN (radio station) (Box 24)
    - Williams, Robert L. (Administrative Dean, Academic Affairs) (Box 24)
    - Willow Run Laboratories (Box 24)
    - Women
      - General (Box 24)
      - Center for Continuing Education of Women (CEW) (Box 24)
      - Discrimination/HEW (Box 24)
    - XYZ-General (Box 24)
  - 1971-1972
    - A-General (Box 25)
    - Academic Affairs Advisory Council (Box 25)
    - Academic Affairs, Office of Vice President for (Allan F. Smith) (Box 25)
    - Accreditation (Box 25)
    - Acknowledgments (Box 25)
    - Acts, Bills, Resolutions, Journals (Box 25)
    - Admissions (Box 25)
    - Affirmative Action Programs
      - General (Box 25)
      - Office of Director, Establishment of (Box 25)
      - Other Schools (Box 25)
      - Women (Box 25)
    - Africa, Corporate Responsibility (Box 25)
    - Afro-American Studies Program (Box 25)
    - Alumni Association (Box 25)
    - American (Box 25)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) (Box 25)
    - American Council on Education (ACE)
      - Affirmative Action (Box 25)
      - General (Box 25)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 25)
    - Anonymous/Asylum (letters) (Box 25)
    - Architecture and Design, College of (Box 25)
    - Argonne Universities Association (Box 25)
    - Association of American Colleges (Box 25)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Council on Federal Relations (Box 25)
    - Association of Governing Boards (Box 26)
    - Athletics (Box 26)
    - Attorney's Office (Box 26)
    - Awards (Box 26)
    - B-General (Box 26)
    - Bentley Chair (Box 26)
    - Bentley Historical Library (Box 26)
    - Black (faculty/students) (Box 26)
    - Brown, Paul W. (Regent) (Box 26)
    - Brown, Robert J. (Regent) (Box 26)
    - Budget and Planning, Office of (Box 26)
    - Bureaus (Box 26)
    - Burning Spear (Box 26)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 26)
    - Bylaws (Box 26)
    - C-General (Box 26)
    - Carnegie Commission on Higher Education (Box 26)
    - Cash, William L., Jr. (Assistant to the President for Human Relations Affairs) (Box 26)
    - Centers
      - Glossary (Box 26)
      - Center for Conflict Resolution (Box 26)
      - International Center (Box 26)
      - University Center for Adult Education (UCAE) (Box 26)
    - Clements Library (Box 26)
    - Closed Courses (Box 26)
    - Coalition for the Use of Learning Skills (CULS) (Box 26)
    - Collections (Box 26)
    - Commendations and Congratulations (Box 26)
    - Committees
      - External (Glossary) (Box 26)
      - Internal (Glossary) (Box 26)
    - Community Colleges (Box 26)
    - Complaints
      - President Fleming (about) (Box 26)
      - General, 3 folders
        - folders 1-2 (Box 26)
        - folder 3 (Box 27)
    - Computer Network (Box 27)
    - Condolence and Illness Letters (Box 27)
    - Consortia (Box 27)
    - Corporate Responsibility (Box 27)
    - Council for Financial Aid to Education (Box 27)
    - Council of Ten (Committee on Institutional Cooperation) (Box 27)
    - Course Evaluation (Box 27)
    - Cudlip, William B. (Regent) (Box 27)
    - D-General (Box 27)
    - Deans, Letters to (Box 27)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 27)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 27)
    - Detroit (Box 27)
    - Development Office/Development Council (Box 27)
    - Disruptions (Box 27)
    - Doezema, Edward R. (Professor) (Box 27)
    - Drugs (Box 27)
    - Dues and Contributions (Box 27)
    - Dunn, Gerald R. (Regent) (Box 27)
    - E-General (Box 27)
    - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 27)
    - Economics Research: Incomes and Collective Bargaining (Box 27)
    - Education, School of (Box 27)
    - EDUCOM (Box 27)
    - Eighteen-Year-Old Vote (Box 27)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 27)
    - Environment (includes ENACT) (Box 27)
    - Estates (Box 27)
    - Evaluation and Examinations Office (Box 27)
    - Exchange Programs (Box 27)
    - Expeditions (University-Involved) (Box 27)
    - Extension Service (Box 28)
    - External Degree Program (Box 28)
    - F-General (Box 28)
    - Faculty Reform Coalition (Box 28)
    - Fauri, Fedele F. (Vice President for State Relations and Planning) (Box 28)
    - Fees (Box 28)
    - Fellowships/Scholarships
      - External (Box 28)
      - Internal (Box 28)
    - Financial Aid, Office of (Box 28)
    - Fleming, Robben W. (President)
      - Accolades (Box 28)
      - Personal (Box 28)
      - Statements and Miscellaneous Notes (Box 28)
    - Flint College (Box 28)
    - Football (Social Activities) (Box 28)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 28)
    - Foreign Student Inquiries (Box 28)
    - Fricke, Benno G. (Director, Evaluation and Examinations Office) (Box 28)
    - G-General (Box 28)
    - Gifts (Box 28)
    - Goebel, Paul G. (Regent Emeritus) (Box 28)
    - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of (Box 28)
    - Grievances (Box 28)
    - H-General (Box 28)
    - Haber, William (Advisor to Executive Officers) (Box 28)
    - Handicapped Students (Box 28)
    - Health Services, University (Box 28)
    - Historical Collections (Michigan Historical Collections) (Box 28)
    - Homosexuals (Box 28)
    - Housing
      - Faculty and Student (Box 28)
      - Black Housing (Box 28)
      - Xanadu House (Box 29)
    - I-General (Box 29)
    - Identification Cards (Box 29)
    - Individualized Instruction (Kellogg Foundation) (Box 29)
    - Institutes
      - External (Box 29)
      - Internal (Box 29)
    - Institutional Research, Office of (Box 29)
    - Introduction, Letters of (Box 29)
    - J-General (Box 29)
    - K-General (Box 29)
    - Kelsey Museum (closing) (Box 29)
    - King (Martin Luther) Fund (Box 29)
    - Kopernik 500th Anniversary Celebration (Box 29)
    - Kunnes, Richard, Dr. (Washtenaw County Community Mental Health Center) (Box 29)
    - L-General (Box 29)
    - Law School (Box 29)
    - Lectures (Glossary) (Box 29)